（ヤサコ）人の世のウワサでは―
According to rumors circulating among some people,
会いたい人のことを
ずっと考えていると
if you think constantly about a person you want to meet,
不意にばったり出会うことが
あるそうです
you'll suddenly end up seeing them.
（フミエ）研究 私も手伝うわ
I'll help you with the research.
（ヤサコ）
私も　同じクラブじゃない
Me too!
We're in the same club after all!
…とは言ってみたものの
But even though we said that,
we really have no idea how to help him out.
何をどうすりゃあ
手伝ったことになるのか
さっぱりだわ…
まずは イリーガルを探すことね
For starters, we need to find an Illegal.
そして そのイリーガルが
Then we have to verify whether or not the Illegals
電脳ナビの異常に
関係あるかどうか調べるのよ
have anything to do with the cybernavis malfunctioning.
そっか
Yeah...
でもイリーガルって
どうやって探すの？
But how do we search for an Illegal?
まずは 古い空間を探すのよ
First of all, we have to search the obsolete Space.
それには交通費 弁当代
But we need to consider the expenses for transport,
food,
それに お菓子代も入れないと
sweets—
（ダイチ）先生！
女子がおしゃべりしてます
Teacher!
The girls are talking in class.
（マイコ）
授業中におしゃべりしないように
Don't talk during class.
（ダイチ･ナメッチ）ニヒヒ～
フン！　すっかりイサコの仕切りね
That group is totally Isako's.
ヤな感じだわ
How disgusting.
Move Out! Coil Investigation
Agency
（ヤサコ）
ねえ さっきの計算
一体なんなの？
Hey, what were those figures you were doing earlier?
（フミエ）
今回の自由研究の経費よ
I was calculating the budget for our research.
もろもろ込みで
お年玉１年分は必要だわ
Including all the various expenses, we'll need one year's otoshidama.
（ヤサコ）
えっ そんなに？
Really? That much?
バナナを
お菓子に含めない計算でね
And I didn't include banana sweets...
メガばあの招集だわ
It's a summons from Mega-baa!
招集？
A summons?
（フミエ）
で なんなのよ？　招集って
So what's this about?
（メガばあ）
うむ 電脳ペットの捜索じゃ
It's a missing pet case.
３丁目のトメさんの
ハムスター マンタが―
Our neighbor, Tome, lost her cyberhamster, Manta.
昨日から行方不明になっとる
She lost track of it yesterday.
私たち いろいろあって
今 忙しいのよ
We already have our hands full with everything that's happened the past few days!
（メガばあ）断ったら
メタタグは今までの倍に値上げじゃ
If you don't help me out, I'll charge 'ya double for metatags.
じゃが 引き受けたら
ボーナスが出るかもしれん
But if you accept this case,
you might even get a bonus.
（ヤサコ）ボーナス？
A bonus?
うむ 実は絡んでおるのじゃ
Yeah. You should know what this case is about:
お宝がな！
A treasure!
（メガばあ）お宝じゃと？
What?! A treasure?
（トメ）うん 光る何かじゃ
Yeah.
It was something shiny.
確かに そんなものを
わしは持っておった
I'm sure I had something like that.
ハッ！　そ… それは
もしかしてキラバグかえ？
Don't... Don't tell me you mean...
a kirabug?
I'm not really sure;
（トメ）
はて？　それは定かではないが
キンキラキンに光り輝く何かじゃ
it was something that was shining.
じゃが わしは
その秘密を覚えておく自信がない
But I felt I wouldn't remember such a secret,
そこでペットのマンタに
記憶させてあるのじゃ
so I recorded it into my pet, Manta.
うーん…
それはキラバグに相違あるまい
There's no doubt it's a kirabug.
ところで
あんた 誰じゃったかのう？
By the way, what's your name again?
キ… キ… キラバグですって！
Wh-What?! A kirabug?!
キラバグって何？
What's a kirabug?
とんでもなく値の張るメタバグよ
It's an amazing and highly-valued metabug!
トメさんは そのお宝の３割を
お礼に支払うそうじゃ
Tome has agreed to pay us a third of the treasure's worth.
３割も！
A third?!
何かと物入りじゃないのかえ？
Don't you have some expenses yourselves?
もっちろん引き受けるわ！
Say no more! I'll take the case!
（ダイチ）見張り？
Patrol?
That's right.
（イサコ）
そうよ もし誰か現れたら―
Should anyone come here,
暗号式を荒らさないように
追い払うのよ
you have to prevent them from deciphering the encryption key.
（ガチャギリ）暗号式？
The... encryption key?
（イサコ）踏むな！
（一同）えっ？
Don't step on it!
そいつはデリケートなんだ
It's delicate stuff.
今回 初めて組んだ暗号だから
It's an encode I just made,
何がきっかけで
誤作動するか分からん
so I don't know whether it'll malfunction or not.
だから 誰も近づけさせるな
That's why you have to make sure no one approaches.
それがお前たちの今日の任務だ
That's your mission for today.
（ダイチ）暗号か
（ガチャギリ）どう使うんだ？
An encryption...
How do you make one?
（イサコ）マニュアルをやる
I'll give you a manual.
壊さなければ
ちょっとは使ってもいい
You can use it for a while,
just don't damage it.
このクソ暑いのに
ずっと ここにいろって言うのかよ
What the hell?!
You want us to stay here in this heat?!
冗談じゃねえ！
You gotta be kidding me!
お前ら 帰って
アイスでも食おうぜ
Guys, let's go home and buy some ice cream on the way.
You dare disobey me?
（イサコ）逆らう気か？
（ダイチ）うっ…
そ… そんなにやりたいなら
お前 自分でやれよ！
If...
If you really want that done,
then do it yourself!
なんだと？
What did you say?
（ダイチ）知ってんだぞ
I know your game!
お前 イマーゴってやつが
使えるんだろ？
You can use that "Imago" thing, can't you?
それでササッとやっちまえば
一発だろ？
One shot of that stuff, and you can make a mess!
頭の悪いヤツは嫌いだわ
I hate stupid people.
（ダイチ）何？
What?
（イサコ）自分たちの腕を見てみろ
Look at your arms.
Do you want to challenge me again?
（イサコ）
もう一度 勝負してあげようか？
今度は何年分がいい？
How many years' otoshidama will it be this time?
（ダイチ）ま… 待て！　分かった
言うとおりにする
W-Wait!
I got it!
I'll do whatever you want!
（イサコ）二度と私に逆らうな
文句を言わずにやれ！
Never disobey me again.
Now shut up and do as I say!
（一同）へ～い
Yes, boss.
（ヤサコ）この辺りね
マンタが目撃されたのって
I heard that Manta was spotted in this area.
（フミエ）みたいね
ここは潰れた会社の土地だから
Yeah, I heard the same thing.
This place is the abandoned site of a company that went bust,
こないだのバスの墓場みたいに
so, like the bus graveyard from the other day,
サッチーが
入り込みにくい場所なのよ
it's not easily accessible to Satchii.
（フミエ）さあ 手分けして捜そう
Okay, let's split up and search.
O-Okay...
（フミエ）
私は こっちを捜してみるわ
I'll look over there.
いる
It's here.
イリーガルだ 間違いない
An Illegal.
There's no doubt about it.
I hope this new combination will work all right.
新しい組み合わせが
うまくいけばいいが…
んっ… おかしいな
空間にゆがみがある
How strange...
There's a distortion in the Space.
式のどこかが壊れたのか？
Did a function break down somewhere?
（ヤサコ）なんだろう？
このひそひそ声みたいなの
What's that raspy noise?
気のせいよね
Nobody's coming, right?
（京子(きょうこ)･ヤサコ）うわー！
京子 あんた
なんで ここにいるの？
Kyoko!
What are you doing here?!
京子も遊ぶ
I wanna play, too!
遊んでるわけじゃないの
I'm not playing at all!
もう… しょうがない子ね
Oh geez, you're a real pest...
ほら このハムスターを捜してるの
Look, I'm searching for this hamster.
それなら そこにいるよ
Oh, you mean that one?
きょ… 京子 待ちなさい！
K-Kyoko!
Wait up!
来た！
Here it is!
よし！　これなら もう
おとりのペットも使わずに―
Good!
This way, I don't have to use a pet as bait,
いつでも呼び出せる
and I can summon it whenever I want!
マンタちゃ～ん どこ？
Manta!
Where are you?
異常なしっす
All clear.
（ダイチ）りょうか～い
Roger.
あ～ くだらねえ仕事
What a boring job.
（ガチャギリ）
でもよ ヤツにぶら下がってれば
But hey,
if we stick with her, we might end up finding a treasure.
何かお宝が
出てくるかもしれないぜ
んっ？　お宝ってなんだよ
What kind of treasure?
キラバグだよ
Kirabugs.
しまった！　鍵をさしたままだ
Damn it!
It escaped with my key!
捕まえた！
お姉ちゃん 捕まえたよ
Got it!
Sis, I got it!
（ダイチ）
キラバグって 普通の30倍の値が
ついたってウワサのか？
Kirabugs...
Do you mean, the ones valued at more than thirty times the regular price?
（ガチャギリ）ああ 駅ビルで
その残骸を見たヤツがいたらしい
Yeah.
Someone happened to see fragments of it at the station.
きっとイサコのヤツも
一獲千金を狙ってるんだ
I'm sure Isako plans to get rich in one go.
これに乗っからない理由はねえぜ
There's no reason why she wouldn't want this prize!
なるほど
I see!
それなら
こんな仕事も楽なもんだぜ
In that case, this job is a piece of cake!
役立たずめ！
Those worthless fools!
やはり 今までどおり
ペットで引き寄せるべきだったか
I should've just used a pet,
as I've been doing up till now!
そうだ！　もしかして あそこに…
That's right!
If by any chance it's over there...
（ヤサコ）京子？
Kyoko!
待て！
Wait!
What's... this?
何… これ？
うわっ…
（イサコ）バカ 早く出ろ！
You idiot! Get out of here, quickly!
しまった！
Damn it!
（ヤサコ）開かないわ
廃工場なのに なんで？
It won't open.
Why? Isn't this factory abandoned?
なんてマヌケなんだ
I'm such an idiot...
I never imagined I'd fall into my own trap!
自分で仕掛けたトラップに
引っ掛かるなんて
A trap?
トラップ？
I would have confined it here
いざというとき
ここに閉じ込める予定だったんだ
in case of an emergency.
Confined what?
閉じ込めるって何を？
イリーガルだ
The Illegal.
自分のほうが閉じ込められるとはな
I can't believe that I ended up here instead.
イリーガルなら
電脳壁で閉じ込められるでしょ？
I thought the only way to confine an Illegal was with cyberweaponry.
なんで扉まで閉めるのよ
So why did you need to close the door?
バッテリーが残っているのに
気づかなかった
I didn't notice it had some battery power left.
それが暗号で
偶然 作動したらしい
Apparently, it moved somehow, thanks to the encode.
I know!
そうだ！　電話で誰か呼べば…
Let's call for help!
Out of Reach
Unable to Connect
（ヤサコ）圏外…
（イサコ）ムダだ
Out of reach...
It's no use.
I blocked the signal from this place on purpose.
こちらからの発信は
遮断してある
But it's possible to receive—
受信はできるがな
Why did you do such a thing?!
なんで そんなことするのよ
Hey, there's a way to get out of here, right?
ねえ 外に出る方法は
あるんでしょ？
There isn't.
ないわ
It's possible to open it from the outside,
外からは開けられるけど
中からはムリよ
but impossible to do so from the inside.
Why?!
なんで？
I didn't predict this situation.
こんなの想定外よ
お前さえ
こんな所に現れなければ
If only you hadn't popped up like that.
So it's my fault?!
私のせい？
天沢(あまさわ)さんがこんなことしてるなんて
私が知るわけないじゃない！
But how could I have known
that you were doing all this in the first place?
フン！
Oh yeah, Kyoko is here, too!
そうだ 京子がいる！
（イサコ）何？
What?
She's around here somewhere.
（ヤサコ）近くにいるのよ
大声で呼んで開け方を教えれば…
If we call for her out loud, and tell her how to open...
Why didn't you say so in the first place?!
それを早く言え！
Over there!
いた！
（イサコ）どこだ？
Where?
Oh, Kyoko...
京子ったら…
んっ… マズい
（ヤサコ）んっ？
This is bad!
Oh no! An Illegal!
ヤダ… イリーガル！
It wants to enter the pet.
ヤツはペットの中に逃げ込む気だ
Enter the pet?
ペットの中？
Illegals can only survive
（イサコ）
イリーガルが生き延びられるのは
in an obsolete Space or inside cybermateria.
古い空間と
電脳生物の体内だけなんだ
It's useless...
ダメだ この回線も違う
This circuit is no good, either.
What are you doing, Isako?
ねえ 何やってるの？　イサコ
Don't call me Isako!
イサコって言うな
S-Sorry.
ご…　ごめんなさい
I'm looking for a way to open the door.
（イサコ）
ドアを開ける方法を探してるんだ
So stop bothering me.
邪魔するな
Listen, Isa—
あの… イサ…
あっ 天沢さん 私…
Amasawa, I—
I don't want to be your friend.
（イサコ）あんたたちと
友達になる気はないわ
I already told you that.
こないだ言ったとおりよ
Oh, is that so?
そ… そうですか
Oh!
そうだ じゃあ 師匠としてはどう？
Then how about becoming my master?
That last time, when you spilled metabugs out of a secret Space,
ほら こないだの
駅ビルの秘密の空間から
メタバグを取り出したんでしょ？
it looked like a magical power...
まるで魔法使いみたいだわ
I'd like to use it, too!
私 憧れちゃう
I beg you, please let me be your disciple!
お願い 弟子にして！
断る！
Absolutely not!
See?
なあ？　こいつは
ちゃんと動きやがる
This stuff really works!
If that girl is after the kirabugs,
あの女が
キラバグを狙ってるとすれば
we just have to be patient.
しばらく我慢の一手だぜ
But the kirabug is just an urban legend, right?
しかし キラバグって
都市伝説じゃないのか？
What urban legend?
どんな都市伝説なんすか？
Supposedly, a legendary hacker obtained the kirabug
ある伝説のハッカーが
そのキラバグを手に入れたんだ
from "the other side".
あっちからな
But when he tried to bring it here,
だが こっちに呼び出した途端
砕けて死んでしまったそうだ
it shattered into pieces and died.
Died?
（ダイチ）死んだ？
キラバグって生き物(もん)なのか？
So it's a living creature?
Yeah.
（ガチャギリ）
ああ その都市伝説ではな
At least according to the legend.
And so, the remains of the kirabug are what we call metabugs.
そして その死んだキラバグの
化石がメタバグなんだ
（一同）へえー
So the kirabug is a living metabug?
じゃあ キラバグは
生きたメタバグってことか
I wonder if he has legs and runs...
足でも生えて走り出すんですかね
Yasako!
ヤサコ どこ？
Where are you?
Hey! Hold it right there!
（ダイチ）おい ここに近づくな！
Daichi!
（フミエ）ダイチ！
なんで ここにいるの？
What are you doing here?
That's my line!
（ダイチ）それはこっちのセリフだ
とっとと帰れ！
Now get the hell outta here!
Shut up!
（フミエ）うるさい！
（一同）うわっ…
C-Cut it out!
や… やめろ！
危ねえじゃねえか！
That's dangerous!
You're in no position
私に指図するなんて
10年 早いわよ
to give me orders!
You're the one who has to leave.
あんたが帰れ！
んん～ あのチビスケのブスエが！
That damn shrimpy Busue!
（イサコ）チェッ これも違う
Not this one, either.
ああ… 暑くなってきたわね
It's getting hotter in here...
（イサコ）話しかけるな
Don't talk to me!
天沢さんってさ
あんまり幸せじゃないでしょ？
Amasawa, you must not be very happy, huh?
人間 幸せに生きるのが一番よ
People should live a happy life.
さすがに天沢さんも
そう思うでしょ？
I bet you think so too, right?
（イサコ）特に そうは思わない
No, I don't.
そ… そうですか
Is...
Is that so...?
手伝おうか？
Do you need some help?
もう しょうがない子ね
What am I going to do with you?
よいしょっと
ほら 外れたわ
Okay, it's free.
天沢さんに
幸せに生きるコツを教えてあげる
I'll teach you a secret for living happily.
人を拒まないことよ
You shouldn't reject people.
なんでも１人でやろうと思っても
決してできないものよ
It's impossible to do everything by yourself in life.
誰だって他人の力が必要なのよ
Everybody needs other people's help.
あんたが他人を拒まないのは
相手のためじゃない
The reason why you don't reject others,
isn't because you're thinking of them.
自分のためだ
（ヤサコ）えっ？
You do it for yourself.
（イサコ）友達と調子を合わせて
意見を合わせて
You adapt yourself in order to live in harmony with other people...
You adapt your point of view...
自分の言いたいことも言えない
そんな幸せならいらないわ
You can't even say what you want...
If that's happiness, no thanks.
京子！
Kyoko!
おい そこの幼児！
Hey, kid!
サブドメインの
キーファイルを解除してくれ
Turn the lock on the subdomain key files off!
それじゃ 聞こえても
意味 分からないわよ
She wouldn't understand that even if she heard you!
じゃあ お前がやれ
Then you do it!
京子！　ここのロックを
か い じょ し て！
Kyoko!
The lock...
u-n-l-o-c-k it!
具体的に言わないと
分かるわけないでしょ
If you don't tell her how to actually do it,
she'll never guess how.
じゃ… じゃあ
ちゃんと説明してよ
Th-Then explain it clearly to her!
ハァ… あの子ったら もう
What am I supposed to do with that girl?
それにしても―
Why is that virus wandering around here?
なんで あんなウイルスが
うろついてるのかしら？
（イサコ）あれはウイルスじゃない
That's not a virus.
（ヤサコ）どういうこと？
What do you mean?
フッ 知りたいか？
You want to know?
Yes.
あれは呪われた生き物
That is
a doomed creature.
呪われた生き物？
A doomed... creature?
（イサコ）空間のゆがみで生まれた
出来損ないの生き物
An incomplete being created from a distortion in the Space.
こっちに出てくる以前の記憶を
すっかりなくしてるけどね
They've completely lost their memories about the time before they came here.
例えば そう…
自分が何者だったのかすら
For example,
what they were in the past.
ヤツらは言ってみれば
あの世の亡者よ
In other words, they're like the inhabitants of the netherworld.
それが消えずに
あてどなく さまよい続けている
They carry on forever, wandering without a goal.
（ヤサコ）なぜペットを襲うの？
Why do they attack pets?
（イサコ）ペットの体など
本当は問題じゃない
The real issue isn't the body of the pet.
そこは単なる避難場所にすぎない
It's just a place to take shelter.
新しい空間では そうしないと
すぐに体が溶けてしまうからだ
In fact, if they don't do so in a new Space,
their body disintegrates.
彼らが本当に欲しいものは別にある
But there's something special they aim for.
自分の正体を
忘れてしまっているのに
Although they've forgotten their nature,
それだけは本能が覚えているんだ
they do remember one thing: their instinct.
それは…
And that is...
人間の子供に近づくという本能
the instinct to get close to kids.
子供に？
To kids?
（イサコ）
ヤツらが本当に入り込みたい場所は
The place they really want to get inside is
子供の電脳体
the cyberbodies of children!
（ヤサコ）
えっ そんな… どうして？
No way...
But why?
知りたいの？　本当に知りたい？
Do you want to know?
Do you really want to know?
な… 何よ
Wh-What is it?
（イサコ）教えてあげる
I'll tell you then.
ヤツらはね 食べるのよ
You must know
that they eat...
子供の魂をね
kids' souls!
魂を？
Souls?
そうよ 内側に潜り込んで
ムシャムシャとね
Exactly.
It sneaks inside your body,
and gnaws away at you!
That's...
そ… そんなことあるわけない
That's completely impossible!
だって イリーガルは
電脳世界のものじゃない
The Illegals are from the virtual world, aren't they?
（イサコ）それがあるのよ
There is a way.
呪われた方法がね
A cursed way...
（イサコ）都市伝説で
語られるだけになってるけど
It's only been reported in urban legends,
実際に食われた子供がいるのよ
but in reality, some kids have actually been eaten.
そんなバカな…
That's... completely absurd...
あんたも気をつけたほうがいい
You'd better be careful, too.
ヤツらの好物は
Their favorite target is
あんたみたいな
おめでたい無防備な子供の魂
the helpless, happy soul of a kid
exactly like you!
やめてよ！
Cut it out!
気をつけな
Watch out.
ヤツらは気づかない間に
忍び寄ってくる
They sneak inside you when you least expect it,
そして食っちまうんだ
and they eat it.
お前の魂をな！
Your soul, got it?
やめて！
Knock it off!
ハハハハッ 信じた？
Did you believe it?
バカね ウソよ
全部 私の作り話
You're such a fool.
It was all a lie.
I made everything up.
作り話？
Made it up...?
あれは あんたの友達が言うとおり
単なるコンピューターウイルスよ
It's exactly like your friend says.
It's just a computer virus.
最近 妙な変異を
起こしてるみたいだけどね
Even if it has been acting strangely recently.
だましたのね！
So you tricked me!
もともとは どこかのハッカーが
ばらまいたそうよ
I heard that a hacker originally spread it,
いろんな機器を
誤動作させるためにね
in order to take down numerous machines.
もう意地悪！
You meanie!
Out of Reach
Unable to Connect
（ヤサコ）あっ
（イサコ）どうした？
What is it?
今 一瞬つながった
（イサコ）なんだと？
It connected for an instant!
What?
おい もう一度 さっきのポーズだ
Hey!
Take that pose again!
足を開け
Spread your legs.
や… やめなさいよ エッチ
Stop touching me, you pervert!
（イサコ）言うことを聞け
きっと電波の漏れがあるんだ
Do as I say!
The signal must be leaking in.
So I'm replacing an antenna?
私ってアンテナ代わり？
あっ キュウちゃんだ！
The Kyuu-chans!
何？　マズいぞ それは…
What?!
We're in big trouble!
（ヤサコ）京子！
（イサコ）そのポーズだ
Kyoko!
That position!
えっ？
（イサコ）動くな
Don't move!
待って！　く… 靴
うわあ～！
Wait!
My shoes...!
ウンチ！
Poop!
おい 幼児 早く戻れ！
そこは崩れるぞ
Hey, kid!
Come over here, quick!
It's gonna fall!
ゆっくり こっちに来るのよ
できる？
Come here... slowly.
You can do it.
普通に歩くの　分かる？
Walk normally.
Got it?
怖くない 一歩ずつよ
Nothing to be afraid of.
Step by step.
そうよ うまいわ
Just like that.
Good girl.
おいで
Come...
Here!
こっちだ 跳べ！
Jump!
Kyoko!
京子！
ハッ… 京子
Kyoko!
ほら じっとして
他に痛いところないわね？
C'mon, dry those tears.
You don't have any other scratches, do you?
（ヤサコ）１人にしてごめんね
Sorry for leaving you alone.
（イサコ）
古い空間を求めて外へ出たか
So it was looking for an obsolete Space, and when it came out...
あのイリーガル
かなりの量のキラバグを含んでいた
That Illegal
had a big kirabug inside it.
逃がすものか
I won't let him get away.
Amasawa, wait.
（ヤサコ）天沢さん 待って
Thank you for helping Kyoko.
京子を助けてくれて… ありがとう
It was nothing.
別に
I wonder...
私たち…
if we really can't be friends.
やっぱり友達になれないのかな？
I...
（イサコ）
それはないと言ったはずよ
already told you so, didn't I?
私が必要なものを
あんたは持ってないわ
You don't have the thing I need.
Is that so...
（ヤサコ）そう…
（イサコ）でも
But...
Nobody in this world really knows
先のことは分からないわ
この世界の誰にも
what will happen next.
What did you say?!
（フミエ）なんですって？
キラバグだなんて
ひと言も言っとらん
I never said the word kirabug.
After all, I don't even remember what I recorded in Manta.
そもそも何をマンタに記憶させたか
わしも覚えとらんのじゃ
Mega-baa!
メガばあ！
Be patient.
まあ 待っとれ　今 解凍中じゃ
I'm uncompressing it now.
Decompressing
I'm sure it's a very valuable item!
絶対 値打ちもんに決まっとる
There it is!
It's on my husband's head.
（フミエ）出た！
（メガばあ）ん… んっ？
（フミエ）頭？
The head?
Oh, I remember now!
おおー 思い出した
The shining thing was my husband's head!
光り物は
わしの旦那の頭 そのものじゃ
What the hell am I supposed to do with a third of this?!
んなもん ３割もらって
どないすんじゃ～！
There's a weak signal coming from an obsolete Space.
わずかに古い空間の反応が出ている
And right next to here is...
この先は…
the school.
学校か
Preview
Next time on Dennou Coil:
The summer festival and the duel.
The Summer Festival and the Duel
See you next time!
（ヤサコ）
次回 「電脳コイル」
〝夏祭り、
そして果たし合い 〞
お楽しみに